sitescanga.com 2010-01-02

# SiteScan™ By EpikOne - A Google Analytics Help, Setup, and Configuration Tool

**SiteScan** **Privacy Policy**

SiteScan collects no personal information about you when you visit our web site unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, we collect and store certain information automatically. Here is how we handle information about your visit to our web site. 

## Sharing and Usage

We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.

Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information, and to reputable, contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you. The latter of which includes periodic notifications on SiteScan and related services. All such notifications include an option to unsubscribe as you feel appropriate. 

##  What We Collect and Store Automatically 

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the web site, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit: 

  * The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our web site. 
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our site. 
  * The date and time you access our site. 
  * The pages you visit. 
  * If you linked to our web site from another web site, the address of that web site. 
  * We use the information we collect to count the number and type of visitors to the different pages on our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors like you. 

##  If You Send Us E-mail 

You may choose to provide us with personal information, such as an e-mail with a comment or question. We use the information to improve our service to you or to respond to your request. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not share our e-mail with any other outside organizations. 

## Links to Other Sites 

Our web site has links to partners and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. 

##  Restriction of Liability 

SiteScan makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this web site and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this web site. No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed or statutory, including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to the contents of this web site or its hyperlinks to other Internet resources. Reference in this web site to any specific commercial products, processes, or services, or the use of any trade, firm or corporation name is for the information and convenience of the public, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by SiteScan.

Please note that Google Analytics™ is the trademark of Google, Inc. and is not affiliated with SiteScan.  Google, Inc. accepts no responsibility, liability and does not provide support to individuals choosing to use this product.  All inquiries regarding SiteScan should be submitted to:  [info@SiteScanGA.com](mailto:info@SiteScanGA.com)

**Copyright 2008   SiteScan is a service mark of EpikOne, Inc.  All Rights Reserved.**
